<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<application>
	<id type="desktop">tuxpusheraf.desktop</id>
	<metadata_license>CC-BY-4.0</metadata_license>
	<project_license>GPL-2.0-only</project_license>
	<name>TuxPusher &amp; Friends</name>
	<summary>Featuring Tux &amp; Friends!</summary>
	<description>
		<p>Like the original but elongated with 512 new objects generated by LUMA GENIE, along with other minor improvements such as rotating coins and a play rate dependent on your coin quantity/value. You can rapid fire silver coins now by holding down left click.</p>
		<p>Push the 6 unique Tux figurines into the gold and silver pockets at the end of the pitch before you run out of gold and silver coins! It's always a gamble, and your starting hand is make or break!</p>
		<p>Game mechanics that will serve you well to know and use to your advantage.</p>
		<ul>
			<li>Getting a gold coin in a silver slot rewards you 2x silver coins.</li>
			<li>Getting a gold coin in a gold slot rewards you 2x gold coins.</li>
			<li>Getting a tux in a slot when you already have the tux gives you 6x gold coins and 6x silver coins.</li>
		</ul>
		<p>Controls: Just move around your mouse and click to release a coin.</p>
		<ul>
			<li>Left Click = Release coin. (hold to auto-place silver coins)</li>
			<li>Right Click = Show/Hide cursor.</li>
			<li>C = Orthographic/Perspective.</li>
			<li>F = FPS to console.</li>
		</ul>
		<p>There is a command line option that allows you to set the coin deployment speed, but also every time you "lose" a game, the new round will start with a faster deployment speed than the last, just to keep things exciting. ;)</p>
	</description>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2024/01/Screenshot_2024-01-11_05-37-09_y4cdE5P.png</screenshot>
		<screenshot>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2024/01/Screenshot_2024-01-11_05-37-55.png</screenshot>
		<screenshot>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2024/01/Screenshot_2024-01-11_05-38-10.png</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<url type="homepage">https://github.com/mrbid/TuxPusherAF</url>
	<releases>
		<release version="1.0" date="2024-01-09" />
	</releases>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
</application>
